wallpaper.net.au 2013-05-10

# Privacy Policy | Wallpaper World

  | 

| 

Privacy Policy  
  
---  
We here at the Wallpaper World regard your privacy as extremely important. We have therefore created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to protecting the privacy of the information you provide us. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.  

Advertisers  
  
Wallpaper World allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [ NetworkAdvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).  

External Links  
  
The Wallpaper World website contains external links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or practices of these websites. However, we will never intentionally link or advertise any website which contains adult or content that is not suitable for minors. If you believe that a link on our website breaches this statement, please inform us by immediately through our Contact Us form.  

Contacting Wallpaper World  
  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us using our Contact Us form.
